>> Jem Young: 我想谈谈服务器。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I wanna talk about server.
服务器执行什么操作 ?
What does a server do?
给你个提示
But give you a hint.
就在名字里
It's in the name.
不是萨姆
Not Sam.
还有谁
Anybody else?
嗯。
Yes.
>> 扬声器 2: [INAUDIBLE] >> Jem Young: 是，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [INAUDIBLE]
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes, that's exactly right.
它为内容提供服务。
It serves content.
这就是服务器所做的。
That is what a server does.
是的，我会以不同的方式回答这个问题。
Yes, I would answer it
a little bit differently.
我会说它是回应要求的
I'd say it responds to requests.
是的，这也是服务器的工作。
Yes, that's also what a server does.
尽管您可以争论响应的定义是一种内容的形式。
Though you can argue the definition
of responses is a form of content.
但是你的可能比较包，挺好的，但是
But yours is probably a bit more
encompassing, which is good, but
它为档案提供服务
it serves files.
这通常是您希望服务器执行的操作。
Like that's usually what
you want a server to do.
它起到了一些作用。
It serves something back.
如果服务器说我 ping 通，什么都没做。
If a server just let's say I pinged it and
didn't do anything.
服务器的重点是什么 ?
What's the point of the server?
他们都是为了所有的目的和目的不存在我的需要
They're like, for all intents and
purposes, it doesn't exist to my needs.
但服务器也只是一个真正强大的计算机，或者
But a server is also just a really,
really powerful computer, or
任何计算机都可以是服务器。
any computer at all can be a server.
您的笔记本电脑可以是服务器。
Your laptop can be a server.
实际上，如果您进行任何本地开发，那么它是一个服务器。
In fact, if you do any sort of
local development, it is a server.
所以当我们想到服务器时，我们通常会想到巨大的服务器机架和
So when we think servers,
we often think giant server racks and
数据农场和所有这些东西
data farms and all these things.
但我的电话可以是服务器任何东西都可以是服务器
But my phone can be a server,
anything can be a server,
只要它响应一个请求和服务内容，它是一个服务器。
as long as it responds to a request and
serving content, it's a server.
让我们做个服务器
So let's make a server,
因为服务器是我们今天要做的
because a server is what we're
gonna be doing today primarily.
是啊让我们做个服务器吧
Yeah, let's make a server.
所以回到维姆
So back to vim.
所以你确定你在
So make sure you're in,
这是一些临时文件夹，我们具有写许可权。
this is some temporary folder
we have write permissions.
如果您可以编写上一项，请切换文件夹或创建新的文件夹。
If you can write last item,
switch folders, or create a new one.
所以只能说 vi simpleServer.js 或您要调用它的任何内容。
So just say vi simpleServer.js or
whatever you want to call it.
>> Jem Young: 我们要写一个裸机服务器。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
we're gonna write a bare bones HP server.
我假定您已安装节点，如果不是 MPM 安装破折号。
I'm assuming you have Node installed,
if not MPM install dash.
其实就是安装节点，但是
Actually just install Node, but
99% 的人已经在计算机上安装了节点。
99% of people have Node installed
in their computer already.
你在Fron趋向大师赛
You're in Frontend Masters.
如果不仅仅是 google 如何安装节点和快速执行该操作。
If not just google how to install Node and
do that real quick.
或者，如果使用 Python ，我们也可以用 Python 做。
Or if using Python we can
do it in Python as well.
Python 实际上更容易启动服务器。
Python is actually even
easier to start a server.
就像用 python 冲刺来启动服务器。
It's like python dash m to start a server.
先把它烧了
But go ahead and fire that up.
我也要做同样的事
And I'm going to do the same thing.